JUSTIN LIU

justintwd@gmail.com +886-982-612-553 blog.justintw.com

I am a **full-stack web developer and DevOps with 6 years industry and 3 years contract,** specializing in scalable cloud architectures for web application and network maintenance. While my work focuses on web engineering, mostly building SPA with front-end framework like Angular, and building RESTful api with back-end framework such as Django or Tornado. For my part-time IT task, I build and maintenance network and various IT service for my company. My nonwork interest ranges widely. By spending free time learning other computer science related subjects such as network security and algorithms, my interest into computer just keeps deepening. Building small tools which makes my life easier is also something I love to do on the weekend. I am from Taiwan and looking for engineer positions in Taiwan.

</> </> SKILLS

IT Service (Proficient) Bind 9, Squid 3, Samba, Nginx, OpenLDAP, FreeRadius, Docker, VPN

HA and Load Balance (Basic) DRDB, Percona DB Cluster, MongoDB Cluster, Virtual IP, Nginx Reverse Proxy

Network (Proficient) Nmap, Shorewall, tshark, iptables, mtr, dig

Web (Back-end) (Intermediate) Diango, Tornado, RabbitMO, Node.is, PHP, RESTful, HTTP Protocol

Web (Front-end) (Basic) Angular, React, jQuery, Bootstrap

Database (Basic) MySQL, MongoDB, Redis

Configuration and laaC (Basic) Puppet, CloudFormation, Terraform

CI / CD (Proficient) Jenkins, Drone

EMPLOYMENT

Seinor Engineer, IIoT Solution Dept., MOXA Inc.

2018-02 — 2018-06

Design and implement CI/CD flow for IIoT product and maintain web backend project.

- Design and Implement CI/CD flow for IIoT product Tools: Drone, Docker, CloudFormation, Terraform
- Maintain Web Backend Project of IIoT product Tools: Flask, Nginx, qunicorn

Principal Engineer, CCP Dept., Openfind Information Technology, Inc.

2017-09 — 2018-01

- EFSS Product Web Development ArkEase Pro Tools: MariaDB, PHP, Django, AngularJS
- Web Stickers Web Sticker Tools: Chrome Extension, AngularJS

Software Engineer, EFSS Dept., Hope Bay Technologies, Inc.

2013-06 — 2017-09

Hope Bay Technologies, Inc. is a startup company since June 2013 owned by Dr. Ben Jai, I involve with building, maintaining network, building various IT service for company, and join many commercial products development.

- Information Systems and Technology
- Built and Maintenance of Network 100+ users Tools: Linux, iptables, VLAN, VPN, netdata, ELK Stack
- Built and Maintenance of Cache Service Transparent proxy and various cache: apt, pypi, npm, docker
- Built and Maintenance of IT Service Service: DNS, LDAP, GitLab, DB Cluster, FreeRadius
- Web developer
- Phone Recording System 900+ users EVI.TW Tools: AWS, MongoDB, web.py, Knockout.js
- IP-PBX Recording System ArkVoice Tools: MongoDB, web.py, Knockout.js, RabbitMQ
- Tera Phone Web File Manager Tera. Mobi Tools: MongoDB, Tornado, React.js, RabbitMQ
- EFSS Product Web Development ArkEase Pro Tools: MariaDB, PHP, Django, AngularJS

Seinor Engineer, CTBU, Delta Electronics

2012-06 — 2013-06

I am a web application developer for data center physical machine management product.

- Data Center Machine Manager Development Tools: Django, Twitter Bootstrap, jQuery
- File Storage Product Development Tools: PHP, Ext. js

EDUCATION

Master, Graduate Institute of Electronics Engineering, National Taiwan University

2010-09 — 2012-06

Bachelor, Department of EE, National Taiwan University of Science and Technology

2006-09 — 2010-06

WRITING

Justin Tech Share Blog, Justin Liu

2017